# **Thomas Wiltshire**

Hello, my name is Thomas. I'm a hard-working, passionate games programmer that is currently living in Ballarat, Victoria. Over the last 3 years, I have been studying at the Academy of Interactive Entertainment (AIE) to obtain a Bachelor of Games and Virtual Worlds (Programming).

Fraser Street Mount Pleasant, VIC 3350

+61 466661042 thomas.wiltshire14@icloud.com thomaswiltshire.com

#### **EDUCATION**

**Bachelor of Games and Virtual Worlds**, Academy of Interactive Entertainment — *Melbourne*, *Victoria* 

January 2017 - December 2019

**Primary School / High School,** Kyabram P-12 College / Kyabram St Augustine's College — *Kyabram, Victoria* 

January 2002 - December 2014

### **EXPERIENCE**

## **Software Developer Trainee**, Advance Computing — *Kyabram*, *Victoria*

January 2016 - December 2016 (1 Year)

I worked at Advance Computing for around a year where I started a Certificate 3 in Information Technology as a part of my traineeship in software development. I learnt a lot during my time at Advance, had many amazing experiences, obtained a greater knowledge of business and got my first real taste of the software development industry.

### **Kitchen Crew Member,** Mc Donald's Australia — *Echuca, Victoria*

March 2015 - January 2016 (1 Year)

I worked at McDonald's Echuca within the kitchen environment, being trained in most aspects. During my time here, I gained irreplaceable skills and experience in teamwork, punctuality, leadership and of course, cleaning and cooking.

# **IT Technicians Assistant (Work Placement),** Kyabram Community and Learning Centre — *Kyabram*, *Victoria*

March 2014 - December 2014 (½ Year)

As a part of my VCAL studies, we were required to find work placement positions for at least one day a week. I worked at KCLC in the IT department helping with various repair jobs, network issues and general computer assistance.

#### **EXPERIENCE AND SKILLS**

Software Development. C#, C++, Lua, HTML/CSS, UWP.

Agile Development Methodology.

Git and Git Terminal Experience.

Knowledge in both PC and Macintosh systems.

Punctual, Polite and Enthusiastic.

Teamwork and Troubleshooting Skills and Experience.

### NOTABLE PROJECTS (FOUND AT THOMASWILTSHIRE.COM)

Zombie Game - Video Game.

Toy Wars - Video Game.

Gypsy's Tale - Video Game / Technical Design Document.

### **REFERENCES**

AS THIS IS A PUBLIC SITE, REFERENCES ARE AVAILABLE ON REQUEST, TO PROTECT REFERENCE INFORMATION!